in this video we're going to look at
在这个视频中，我们将要看
some additional solution concepts other
其他一些解决方案概念
than the Nash equilibrium so these are
比纳什均衡，所以这些是
different ways of talking about which
不同的谈论方式
outcomes of a game make sense from a
游戏的结果从
game theoretic perspective first of all
博弈论的观点
I want to talk about a solution concept
我想谈一谈解决方案的概念
called iterated removal of dominated
称为反复删除主导
strategies and I want to illustrate this
策略，我想说明一下
by the example of grace shown in this
以这个例子中的恩典为例
picture here who decided to jump out of
决定跳出图片的人
a plane to celebrate her 91st birthday
一架庆祝她91岁生日的飞机
so I want to think about a game between
所以我想考虑一下
Grace and the guy that she chose to
格蕾丝和她选择的那个人
strap herself to who you can also see in
把自己绑在你也可以看到的人身上
the picture and in particular I want to
图片，尤其是我想
think about his decision of whether to
考虑他的决定是否
pack the parachute safely or not and her
降落伞是否安全打包，她
decision about whether to jump out of
关于是否跳出的决定
the plane or not now in principle she
原则上她现在还是不在飞机上
might worry that he would choose not to
可能会担心他会选择不
pack the parachute safely and she would
安全地打包降落伞，她会
choose to jump out of the plane and if
选择跳出飞机，如果
that were to happen then she would never
那将要发生，那么她将永远不会
get to celebrate her 92nd birthday but
庆祝她的92岁生日，
you can see in fact she did choose and
你可以看到事实上她确实选择了
indeed she landed safely and her choice
的确，她安全着陆并且选择
was a good one
是一个好人
so how was she able to reason that this
所以她怎么能推理出
was sensible well if she looked at the
如果她看着
payoffs of the game she would see that
游戏的收益，她会看到
that this guy let's call him Bruce
这个家伙叫他布鲁斯
Bruce's action of not packing the
布鲁斯不包装行李箱的行为
parachute safely was very bad not only
安全降落伞不仅非常糟糕
for grace but also for himself in fact
为了恩典，也为了自己
it was a dominated strategy and knowing
这是一个主导的策略，并且知道
that he's rational grace reasoned that
他的理性宽限理由
he would never play a dominated strategy
他永远不会扮演主导策略
and so she was able to change the game
这样她就能改变比赛
by removing this dominated strategy and
通过删除这一主导策略，
instead to reason that she only had to
而是说她只需要
care about the remainder of the game in
在乎游戏的其余部分
which his dominated strategies didn't
他的主导策略没有
exist this is the idea of iterated
存在，这是迭代的想法
removal of dominated strategies which
删除主导策略
you'll hear about more formally later
您稍后会听到更多正式消息
secondly I'd like to revisit our
其次，我想回顾一下我们的
question of soccer goal kicking and I'd
踢足球的问题，我会
like to ask is it really the
想问的是真的吗
is that when a player prepares to take a
是当玩家准备接受
penalty kick he's really solving for the
罚球，他真的解决了
Nash equilibrium now we did see
纳什均衡现在我们确实看到了
experimental evidence that shows that
实验证据表明
the Nash equilibrium is a pretty good
纳什均衡是相当不错的
description of what actually happens in
实际发生的情况的描述
these situations but is it the case that
这些情况，但事实是
the players are really thinking about
玩家们真的在考虑
the idea of Nash equilibrium that
纳什均衡的思想
doesn't seem right it seems like the
似乎不正确，好像
players are thinking about how best to
玩家正在考虑如何最好地
kick the ball into the goal in order to
将球踢入球门以
hurt the other guy as much as possible
尽可能伤害另一个人
or in order to do as well for themselves
或者为了自己做得好
as possible it turns out that this isn't
事实证明这不是
an accident in the case of zero-sum
零和的情况下发生事故
games these three ideas doing as well
游戏这三个想法也做得很好
for yourself as possible hurting the
为自己尽可能的伤害
other player as much as possible and
尽可能多的其他玩家
being in Nash equilibrium all turn out
处于纳什均衡状态
to coincide finally I want to revisit
恰好最后我想重温
the battle of the sexes and ask is it
性别之战，问是
really the case that as we saw before
确实如我们之前所见
with the Nash equilibria of this game
这场比赛的纳什均衡
were doomed either to an unfair outcome
注定要么得到不公平的结果
where one member of the couple always
一对夫妻中总是有一个
gets their preferred activity or a miss
得到他们喜欢的活动或错过
coordination where sometimes the the two
有时两者在哪里协调
members of the couple end up doing
这对夫妇的成员最终做
different activities it doesn't seem
似乎没有不同的活动
like this is a good model of how people
像这样是人们如何做的好榜样
really do solve disputes like this
确实确实解决了这样的纠纷
between themselves so I want to think
彼此之间，所以我想
about a new solution concept called
关于一个称为“
correlated equilibrium in which we don't
相关均衡，我们不这样做
have this problem and were able to
有这个问题，并能够
achieve fairness without miss
公平无误
coordination
协调